<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Releases on Fuel</title><link>https://theseion.github.io/Fuel/releases/</link><description>Recent content in Releases on Fuel</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://theseion.github.io/Fuel/releases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://theseion.github.io/Fuel/releases/1.9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://theseion.github.io/Fuel/releases/1.9/</guid><description>Version 1.9 # 8 March 2013
Announcement # We are happy to announce Fuel 1.9.
The default set of packages of this version already comes in Pharo 2.0, so you it&amp;rsquo;s not necessary to install it there. However, Fuel also works out-of-the-box in Pharo from 1.1 up to 2.0, as well as in Squeak 4.1 up to 4.4. You can see our documentation for complete installation and use guides.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://theseion.github.io/Fuel/releases/1.8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://theseion.github.io/Fuel/releases/1.8/</guid><description>Version 1.8 # 26 May 2012
We are proud to announce Fuel 1.8 with a lot of new features and documentation. Of course, we don&amp;rsquo;t stop working but it was time to freeze a stable version.
Fuel works out of the box in Pharo from 1.1 up to 2.0 (checked at #20094). Please check our Documentation for complete installation and use guides.
Below there are some remarkable changes.
Much more complete user guides.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://theseion.github.io/Fuel/releases/1.8.1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://theseion.github.io/Fuel/releases/1.8.1/</guid><description>Version 1.8.1 # 26 May 2012
Announcement # We want to announce Fuel release 1.8.1.
This release includes one fix: serialization / materialization of Date objects. The rest of the work went into making fuel work with as many images as possible. All tests run green.
Supported and tested images: Pharo 1.1.1, 1.1.2, 1.2, 1.3, 1.4, 2.0 and Squeak 4.1, 4.2, 4.3, 4.4.
Have fun!
Description same as 1.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://theseion.github.io/Fuel/releases/1.7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://theseion.github.io/Fuel/releases/1.7/</guid><description>Version 1.7 # 14 October 2011
We have released the new version 1.7 of Fuel. The list of changes includes performance optimizations, design clean-ups, and new features.
The FLSerializer and FLMaterializer API has changed. They are no longer implementing the algorithms but are a kind of Façade. Developer guides with examples: Getting Started and Customizing the graph. Serialization substitutions: &amp;ldquo;Store this object instead of me.&amp;rdquo; Global sends: &amp;ldquo;Restore me by sending this selector to this global&amp;rdquo; Versioning the stream: We prefix the stream with a version number that should match when loading.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://theseion.github.io/Fuel/releases/1.6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://theseion.github.io/Fuel/releases/1.6/</guid><description>Version 1.6 # 19 August 2011
Hello!
I want to announce in this post the new release version 1.6. This version does not add any new concrete functionality but has two main achievements: a performance improvement and a design clean up.
Many changes included in this release are part of a design clean up. They are a necessary step forward to new functionalities that are coming soon. They make code more understandable.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://theseion.github.io/Fuel/releases/1.5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://theseion.github.io/Fuel/releases/1.5/</guid><description>Version 1.5 # 6 July 2011
I am happy to announce the new release version 1.5. Below is the list of changes. In next days we will update the home page with current state. For example, we have much more to show in benchmarks section. Of course, we have many ideas and new issues to keep working on Fuel.
Initialize instances after materialization implementing #fuelAfterMaterialization. Ignore transient instance variables overriding #fuelIgnoredInstanceVariableNames.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://theseion.github.io/Fuel/releases/1.4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://theseion.github.io/Fuel/releases/1.4/</guid><description>Version 1.4 # 1 June 2011
Opening our News section, this post announces a new release version in ConfigurationOfFuel. It is the 1.4 and includes this list of changes:
Serialization in memory. Important refactorings done in various hierarchies and protocols. Hack to avoid several OrderedCollection &amp;raquo; makeRoomAtLast during deserialization. Small code cleanups. To expand on the topic of serialization in memory, I give an example:
aByteArray := FLSerializer serializeInMemory: sourceObject.</description></item></channel></rss>